indigg.com 2013-06-08

# Privacy « Indigg Social News

## Privacy Policy

Indigg takes individual privacy very seriously. We are also aware of the threats to your security and privacy on the Internet. Please take a few moments to review the steps that Indigg takes to ensure your privacy and security while giving you the best possible customer service as you use our web sites. 

We may collect personal information, including email addresses, when individuals register to use the Indigg website and services, post a link to the Indigg website or submit questions, comments or bug reports. We may also, at times, collect our users IP addresses and information regarding our users use of our website and services. We may use such IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our website and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Service. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type. 

When you sign-up with Indigg, we will add your e-mail address into a database. We do not give email addresses to outside companies. We will also never rent or sell out any email addresses. 

When you register with Indigg, you will automatically receive a welcome message, and tips and tricks on how to get the most out of Indigg and other services that may be of interest to you. At any time, you can opt out of these communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link contained in the emails. 

In order to offer and provide optimized and personalized services, we use cookies to store and sometimes track information about our users. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a users browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a users computer hard drive. 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older 

We donot tolerate any racism, anti-religion, hatred, abusive and offensive pictures and news links. Which may harm sentiments of a community or any invividual, violate privacy or human rights. If discovered or informed will be terminated immediately. 

Visit your Indigg Options page to edit your profile and other information. When you are signed in, Indigg page headers will include a link to Settings. You can delete all of your links and personal information from the Indigg Options page. 

Indigg reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization from the appropriate users to do otherwise. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website or your dealings with this Indigg, you can send us an e-mail via contact form.
